# **UĞUR HAMZAOĞLU**



#### **Personal**

- Phone number 05372656029
- Email
  ugur.hmz52@gmail.com

  Date of birth
- 26-04-1994

   Nationality
- Exempt

  Marital status

  Single
- Website https://github.com/ugurhmz
- LinkedIn
  https://www.linkedin.com/in/ugurhamzaoglu/

## Interests

- Coding
- Muay Thai
- Camping
- Swimming
- Computer Games

Hi, I care about <u>clean code</u>. I attach great importance to <u>team harmony and cooperation</u>. Also I have been doing sports for 5 years and I love camping and swimming, coding and to drink coffee.

My Tech Stacks: Java, Spring Boot, JavaScript, Vue.js, Python, Django, Swift, UlKit, SwiftUI, MongoDB, PostgreSQL

# Work experience

iOS Developer

Aug 2022 - Aug 2023

FDN Soft, Ankara / Bilkent (Cyber Park)

- BİREVİM development, bug fix, store <u>release</u>(UIKit)
- Param development, bug fix (UIKit)
- Kredim development, bug fix and store release (UIKit)
- TCDD Development (UIKit)

Tech stacks: Swift (UIKit), SwiftyJSON, R.swift, Dropdown, Firebase, JGProgressHUD, ImageSlideshow, PhoneNumberKit, SwiftyGif etc..

## Java Full Stack Developer

Oct 2021 - Feb 2022

IND Software Information Technology Industry and Trade Co., İstanbul / Üsküdar

- OMIS Project = Managing the workflow of the units within Istanbul Üsküdar, Sultangazi Municipality via the web, bug fix, dev.
- R&D Project = Bug fix, development

Tech Stacks = Java (Spring Boot), JavaScript (Vue.js), PostgreSQL, Vue.JS based Quasar framework also Go.js

#### **Electrical Engineer Intern**

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020

Turkish Hard Coal Enterprise Institution, Zonguldak/Merkez

High Voltage Operation Directorate

## Crew Member

Jun 2017 - Sep 2017

The Wendy's Company, USA / Boston / MA / Hyannis/ Cape Cod

· French fries and chicken cooker

### **Education and Qualifications**

# **Electrical and Electronics Engineering**

Sep 2014 - Jun 2021

Karabük University, Karabük

Card Pass System by ARDUINO

# Side Projects

Swift UIKit = Shopping App/MVVM, Ugurs Dessert Shop/MVVM-R, Authentication App /MVVM-R

Spring Boot: User Management System(Full Stack), REST CRUD

Node.Js: Node.js - E-Commerce-RestAPI